now libraries are one type of dependency
现在图书馆是一种依赖
in IntelliJ IDEA that are typically
在IntelliJ IDEA中通常
packaged either in a jar or some type of
包装在罐子或某种类型的
archive the IDE will access it will
存档IDE将对其进行访问
index go into all the API endpoints and
索引进入所有API端点，
it'll supply that to you as you're
它会为您提供
writing your code and then it'll use
编写代码，然后将其使用
that the same archive to build your
用相同的档案建立您的
project and deploy it depending on the
项目并根据其部署
scope you provide it so so in this
您提供的范围是这样的
lesson I'd like to quickly go over three
我想快速讲完三课
or four things related to libraries so
或与图书馆有关的四件事
if you open up your budget structure
如果您打开预算结构
dialog again and I'll select one module
再次对话框，我将选择一个模块
inside my project and this is the lowest
在我的项目中，这是最低的
level which you can define a library at
您可以在以下级别定义库的级别
and I can add one or more libraries from
我可以从中添加一个或多个库
here inside the dependencies section of
在这里的依赖项部分
my module settings so I can add a new
我的模块设置，以便我可以添加新的
library here and from here I can select
在这里和这里我可以选择图书馆
one of the project libraries which is
项目库之一是
defined at the project level a global
在项目级别定义一个全局
library which is defined over all the
在所有
projects inside my IDE and an
我的IDE中的项目
application server specific library
应用服务器专用库
which is related to the application
与应用程序有关
server that I'm using to deploy this
我用来部署此服务器
module so here I'll select a tomcat
模块，所以在这里我将选择一个tomcat
library and they'll add this library and
库，他们将添加该库并
now I can figure the scope for that
现在我可以确定范围
library as well be that at the compile
库以及在编译时
time during testing and runtime and so
测试和运行时的时间等
forth now you can add a library to
现在，您可以向
project level as well so if you go to
项目级别也是如此，如果您去
your project setting you can go to
您的项目设置，您可以转到
libraries here you can add a new Java
您可以在此处添加新的Java库
library either from maven or from on
来自Maven或来自的库
disk and so if you have one you'd like
磁盘，所以如果您有一个磁盘
to download from maven repository and
从Maven存储库下载并
you can type in say a logging framework
你可以输入一个日志框架
and it will search the maven
它将搜索专家
repositories for a framework that
框架的存储库
matches its keyword and you can say
匹配其关键字，您可以说
select the first one and download that
选择第一个并下载
to a particular location on disk select
选择磁盘上的特定位置
the sources and the Java Docs if you'd
源代码和Java文档（如果您愿意）
like and you can click OK now will
喜欢，您可以单击确定，现在将
download that to my local machine here
将其下载到我的本地计算机上
from maven now if you'd like to add is
如果您想添加的话，现在从Maven
library to any modules at this time you
库到此时的任何模块
can go ahead and select them click OK
可以继续并选择它们，然后单击“确定”。
and then that library will be
然后那个图书馆将是
automatically configured to work with
自动配置为与
both
都
particular modules inside your project
项目中的特定模块
and finally you can add a new library at
最后，您可以在添加新的库
the platform level or across all the
平台级别或所有
projects inside or IDE you can do that
内部项目或IDE，您可以执行此操作
by selecting global libraries here and
通过在此处选择全局库
then adding a new one from Java here and
然后在这里从Java添加一个新的
say we have one on disk and you can add
说我们的磁盘上有一个，您可以添加
that directly here and it'll be added
直接在这里，它将被添加
across all your projects inside the IDE
在IDE中的所有项目中
it will have access to that so that
它可以访问到
pretty much covers working with
几乎涵盖了
libraries on IntelliJ IDEA if you have
如果您有IntelliJ IDEA上的库
any further questions you can always add
您可以随时添加任何其他问题
the comments section below
下面的评论部分
thank you for watching and develop with
感谢您的观看和发展
pleasure
乐趣